[{"answer": "\"That's it?...just", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "\"I don't know the meaning of the word...Seriously, impudence. What does that mean", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "\"Colonel my friend, that place. Two", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "\"I may be a lotta things...but I'm no Tok'ra", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "\"How's that workin' out for you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "\"Good", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "\"No, I'm not", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "\"No, I'm not. I am consoling a friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "\"And then what", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "\"You don't know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "\"my friend, so help me, if you start talkin' like Oma..", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "\"Sounds like my friend to me..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "\"Okay...let's take this one step at a time. This has to be something you want. I can't do this for you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "\"One step at a time", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "\"It used me", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "\"I don't know! And I don't care", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "\"Told you I'd come back", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "\"I am..", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "\"How many more times do you think you can go into that sarcophagus before it starts changing you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "\"I wouldn't be here if I didn't believe you could do it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "\"Damn straight! I'd have busted you out...blown this rat hole to hell and made sure that so", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "\"They'd have a hell of a fight on their hands..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "\"Why would he so blithely betray his master", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "\"Are you suggesting that my friend engaged in an affair with this slave in order to gain access to her master's quarters", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "\"Nothing", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "\"I don't know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "\"Was it to steal the slave from me", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "\"Did my friend believe a slave could know my secrets? There's something else you're hiding from me", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "\"You were right. There's always a way out...at least there's always a chance. You're journey isn't over, my friend, not yet", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "\"I didn't do anything...it was, um, my friend and Teal'c...and, uh, my friend, too", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "\"You're just gonna have to trust me", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Abyss.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "\"I'm gonna be fine", "qsentId": 32}]